http://www.floridaeverblades.com/en/info/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement is applicable to floridaeverblades.com and all its affiliates.The Florida Everblades' policy is to respect and protect the privacy of our users.The Florida Everblades do not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such personally identifiable information may be gathered from a contest or sweepstakes registration, the registration process for subscription sites or services and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), suggestions, voting/polling activities and transactional areas.Personally identifiable information on individual users will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection. At such points of collection, the user will have the opportunity to indicate whether he or she would like to "opt out" of receiving promotional and/or marketing information about other products, services and offerings from the Florida Everblades and/or any third parties. Further, notwithstanding any opt out of promotional information by the user, the Florida Everblades reserves the right to contact a subscriber regarding account status, changes to the subscriber agreement and other matters relevant to the underlying service and/or the information collected.The Florida Everblades may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the Florida Everblades' rights or property, other Florida Everblades users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. The Florida Everblades may disclose user information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.The Florida Everblades reserve the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banners. The Florida Everblades will provide only aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. Also, users should be aware that the Florida Everblades may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through the Florida Everblades' site. The Florida Everblades are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information.Additionally, users should be aware that when they voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the bulletin boards or in the chat areas of the Florida Everblades' sites, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in the user's communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of the Florida Everblades.Users also should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of the Florida Everblades' internet servers or through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising. Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users should be aware that the Florida Everblades cannot or does not control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for the Florida Everblades. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available on the Florida Everblades' site.Upon request, the Florida Everblades will allow any user to "opt out" of further promotional contacts at any time. Additionally upon request, the Florida Everblades will use reasonable efforts to allow users to update/correct personal information previously submitted which the user states is erroneous to the extent such activities will not compromise privacy or security interests. Also, upon a user's request, the Florida Everblades will use commercially reasonable efforts to functionally delete the user and his or her personal information from its database; however, it may be impossible to delete a user's entry without some residual information because of backups and records of deletions.The foregoing policies are effective as of October 2018. The Florida Everblades reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.By using this site, you signify your assent to the Florida Everblades Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the Florida Everblades' sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.Children's Privacy Statement (users under 13 years old)In general, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 via the Web site, and we use age screening mechanisms to help prevent children from posting data on the Web site, such as in our message boards.From time to time, we may offer children the opportunity to enter promotions or contests via the Web site. In each case, the child will be asked only to provide an email address, as well as his or her parent's email address. Upon receipt of the information, we will send an email to the parent indicating that the child has registered, providing information on the program and giving instruction on how the parent can remove the child from the contest. We will then use the information only to notify the contest winners and their parents that they have won. We require that the winner's parent provide us with all information needed to award the prize. Information collected during the contest will not be used or stored after the contest ends, other than as needed for legal requirements in connection with the promotion. In no event will the Florida Everblades collect any information from children in connection with a promotion other than email address and parent's email address. In no event will Florida Everblades use the information other than for purposes of awarding contest prizes.If you have questions or concerns regarding this Web site's privacy statement, you should first contact the company at 239-948-7825.The ECHL and its other member clubs, nor any of their respective officers, directors, governors, owners, other officials, partners, partnerships, principals, employees, affiliates and other related entities, servants, agents, representatives, successors and assigns, have any control of, or responsibility or liability for, our use, disclosure, storage or transmission of any information collected through our websites.
3C28B153-9335-47C6-8182-EDA512A3BB12
Created with sketchtool.
Star 2 Copy
Created with Sketch.
83849D66-8CC8-47EF-8FF3-576CCFD2EB58
Created with sketchtool.
Artboard
Created with Sketch.
Reading Royals R Logo (1)
Group 106
Created with Sketch.
mavs_circle_logo
Created with Sketch.
K-Wings Color
Created with Sketch.
Fav_icon@1x
Created with Sketch.
Icon / Social / Android@3x
Created with Sketch.
icon-dropdown
Created with Sketch.
Check
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
Created with Sketch.
ADIRONDACK_THUNDER_primary_logo_REV2018@1x
Created with Sketch.
echllogoeps
Created with Sketch.
Group 18 Copy
Created with Sketch.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
team-logo / WIN
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PW
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / LOST
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PL
Created with Sketch.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
7CB4E955-9512-49F4-B03B-933CF03CA2FD
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Search/1000
F3916FC0-768E-4027-A1D5-CC66110459CF
Created with sketchtool.
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Attachment/1000
Created with Sketch.
CB_Linked_Icon_Arrow
